(Raj:)Oh, my God, oh, my
God, oh, my God.
(Howard:)Will you please relax?
I can't take it, dude.
(Bernadette:)You okay?
No, I'm not okay.
I feel like
(Raj:)I'm gonna jump out of my skin.
(Bernadette:)I told you
not to wax down there.
(Bernadette:)It's itchy when it grows back.
(Raj:)I'm worried about
the New Horizons space probe.
(Bernadette:)What's he talking about?
(Howard:)Nine years ago
he was part of a team
(Howard:)that launched a spacecraft
to collect data about Pluto.
(Howard:)It's finally close enough, so
(Howard:)this morning
it turned itself on.
(Raj:)We hope.
(Raj:)The signal has to travel
over three billion miles.
(Raj:)So it's gonna be hours before
we know if it even survived.
(Howard:)Now we get to see him flip out
because he's worried
(Howard:)it was demolished by space ice.
(Raj:)Space ice is no joke.
(Raj:)I can't even watch
Frozen anymore.
(Amy:)Ooh, the philharmonic
is playing Beethoven downtown.
Yeah, well, before
you say yes,
(Sheldon:)it's not the movie
about the big dog.